

PROFILE

Graphic Designer who cares about making the best web and mobile product experiences, by applying expertise in User Interface (UI), User Experience (UX), Information Architecture (IA), and Interaction (IX) Design trends. Tech-savy and creative.

Kaatse Mullebrouck

kaatje.mullebrouck@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO

Personal Website

LinkedIn

Behance

behance.net/Kaatje_M

Github

Gitbook

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Applications

Adobe Illustrator • Adobe InDesign • Adobe Muse • Invision • SketchApp

Computer Languages

HTML5/CSS3 • Java (basic) • JavaScript (basic)

Platforms

Mac OS • Windows

PERSONAL SKILLS

Languages
Dutch • English • French

EDUCATION

Graphic & Interactive Design

Foothill College, Los Altos Hills, CA

Bachelor in Education

June 2008

Katholieke Hogeschool Zuid-West

Textile Design

WORK EXPERIENCE & PROJECTS

2+ years Design & Marketing Experience, 10+ years customer service & work experience

UI Components Library

April 2016 – present

Creating and designing User Interface Library.

Freelance Web Designer - SV Techsol

February 2016 - present

Redesigned the SV Techsol website to emphasize the company's mission. By implementing the new layout and site structure, the potential customer will have easier access to information what benefits the customer as well as the company and is a huge timesaver for both parties.

Care For WebDesigning

January 2016 - present

Project, I am currently working on, to make the bridge between designers and software engineers smaller by providing a practical guide for beginners and seasoned designers on how to design for web.

Care For Designing

January 2013 - present

During my free time. I like to work on my personal growth by improving my skills in programs like SketchApp, Corel Painter or learn technical languages like HTML5/ CSS, JavaScript, ...

Care For WebDesigning

January 2015 - March 2015

Designing and producing a real-world graphic design campaign for a seafood restaurant by researching and implementing the customers needs. During the campaign, I worked towards weekly deadlines with the focus on quality, resolved several difficulties by research and redesign, listened and implemented feedback from peers and customer, delivered a successful campaign and presentation within a certain timeframe.

Freelance Graphic Designer & Marketing - Automobuild 2012 - present

Produced a variety of marketing collateral (flyers, brochures, coupons, ...) for promotional activities to make customers aware of certain events. Formatted text and graphics for blog posts and newsletters for social media outlets to gain, successfully, more traffic on the website, as well as in the store.

CERTIFICATIONS

Codeschool.com

June 2015 - present

Adventures in Web Animations • Fundamentals of Design • Front End Foundations • Front End Formations • Journey Into Mobile • CSS Cross Country • JavaScript Road Trip Part 1 & 2

Lynda.com

2014 - present Foundations of Drawing